Guide to the Fales Manuscript Collection circa 1700-2000 MSS.001
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Letter sized boxes
  - Gordon, Charles William (1860-1937) (Ralph Connor, pseud.), undated (Box 70, Folder 15e)
  - Gore, Catherine Gracie Frances (1799-1861): 8 Letters, 2 Mats, undated (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - Gormon, Herbert Sherman (1893-1954): 2 Letters, undated (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - Gosse, Edmund (Sir Edmund William) (1849-1928): 1882-1899 (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - Gosse, Edmund (Sir Edmund William) (1849-1928): 1900-1926; undated (Box 70, Folder 19)
  - Gosse, Edmund (Sir Edmund William) (1849-1928): P.C., envelope, MS.?, undated (Box 70, Folder 20)
  - Gosse, Edmund (Sir Edmund William) (1849-1928): MS. [Proof] The Life of Swinburne, undated (Box 70, Folder 21)
  - Gosse, Philip (1879-1959): Memoirs of a Camp-Follower, Volume 1, undated (Box 70.A, Folder data_value_missing_704ab58b93d36d58f18f4935dd84f7d7)
  - Gosse, Philip (1879-1959): Memoirs of a Camp-Follower, Volume 2, undated (Box 70.B, Folder data_value_missing_da15286ceae8875ba0cb847539a34a2a)
  - Gosse, Philip (1879-1959): A Naturalist Goes to War, undated (Box 70.C, Folder data_value_missing_f7c90d3e1aad5a5a880d61acc05f56bd)
  - Gosse, Philip (1879-1959): The Squire of Walton Hall, undated (Box 70, Folder data_value_missing_56372cb89b4ed3dd9d63ece14579a421, Box 70.D)
  - Gosse, Philip (1879-1959): St. Helena 1502-1938, undated (Box 70.E, Folder data_value_missing_6453d2d468b658300d9301ba961dbe68)
  - Gosse, Nellie [nee´ Epps], undated (Box 70.5, Folder 1)
  - Gosse, Philip (1879-1959), undated (Box 70.5, Folder 2)
  - Gosse, Philip (1879-1959): E. H. Aitken Letters, undated (Box 70.5, Folder 3)
  - Gosse, Philip (1879-1959): Letters to P.G., undated (Box 70.5, Folder 4)
  - Gosse, Philip (1879-1959): Clippings, undated (Box 70.5, Folder 5)
  - Gott, John, Bishop of Truro (1830-1906); Gould, Jay (1836-1892), undated (Box 70.5, Folder 6)
  - provenance file moved to Fales admin files (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Gould, Joe (1889-1957): Notebook (January - May 31, 1943) (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Gould, Joe (1889-1957): Notebook (July 26 - August 27, 1944), 1943 (Box 71, Folder 3a)
  - Gould, Joe (1889-1957): Notebook (December 10 - January 31, 1944), December 10 1943 – January 31, 1944 (Box 71, Folder 3b)
  - Gould, Joe (1889-1957): Notebook (February 1 - April 30, 1944) (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Gould, Joe (1889-1957): Notebook (November 1, 1944 - June 30, 1945), 1944-45 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Gould, Joe (1889-1957): Notebook (July - August 1945) (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Gould, Joe (1889-1957): Notebook (September 24 - November 20?, 1945) (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Gould, Joe (1889-1957): Notebook (December 10, 1945 - April 28, 1946), 1945-1946 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Gould, Joe (1889-1957): Notebook (April 29 - August 13, 1946) (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Gould, Joe (1889-1957): Notebook (August 14 - December 29, 1946) (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Gould, Joe (1889-1957): Notebook (December 30, 1946 - May 28, 1947), 1946-47 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Graham, Robert Bontine Cunninghame (1852-1936): 1890-1928 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Graham, Robert Bontine Cunninghame (1852-1936): 1929-30 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Graham, Robert Bontine Cunninghame (1852-1936): 1931-33 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Graham, Robert Bontine Cunninghame (1852-1936): 1933-35; undated (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Graham, Robert Bontine Cunninghame (1852-1936): Miscellaneous Notes and Clips, undated (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Graham, Stephen: MS. Pictures of my Friends [part 1], undated (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Graham, Stephen: MS. Pictures of my Friends [part 2], undated (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Graham, Elspeth (Thompson), undated (Box 72, Folder 8a)
  - Grahame, Kenneth, undated (Box 72, Folder 8b)
  - Grand, Sarah (pseud. of Mrs. David Chambers McFall, nee´ Frances Elizabeth Bellenden Clarke) (1862-1943), 1894-1913 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Grant, Ethel (Mumford), undated (Box 72, Folder 10a)
  - Grant, Robert (1852-1940), undated (Box 72, Folder 10b)
  - Granville-Barker, Harley Granville (1877-1946), undated (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Graves, Alfred Perceval (1846-1931), undated (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Graves, Robert (1895- ), undated (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Gray, David (Scots poet) (1838-1861), undated (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Gray, William P., II: 1 Letter to T. H. Greider, undated (Box 72.5, Folder 1)
  - Gray, William P., II: MSS. Where Went the Yello Brick Road?: A Fairy Story and A Few Poems, undated (Box 72.5, Folder 2)
  - Gray, William P., II: MS. Window on the World, undated (Box 72.5, Folder 3)
  - Gray, William P., II: MSS. Tome 2 - (Poems), undated (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Gray, William P., II: MSS. Tome 3 - (Poems), undated (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Gray, William P., II: MSS. Tome 4 - (Poems), undated (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Gray, William P., II: MSS. Tome 5 - (Poems), undated (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Gray, William P., II: MSS. Tome 6 - (Poems), undated (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Gray, William P., II: MSS. Tome 7 - (Poems), undated (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Gray, William P., II: MSS. Tome 8 - (Poems), undated (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Greenberg, Samuel (Bernard) (1894-1917): MSS. List, undated (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Greenberg, Samuel (Bernard) (1894-1917): MSS. A, undated (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Greenberg, Samuel (Bernard) (1894-1917): MS. Apology Sonnets, undated (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Greenberg, Samuel (Bernard) (1894-1917): MS. Apology Sonnets [in notebook], undated (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Greenberg, Samuel (Bernard) (1894-1917): MSS. B, undated (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Greenberg, Samuel (Bernard) (1894-1917): MSS. C, undated (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Greenberg, Samuel (Bernard) (1894-1917): MS. Capablanka [drama] [see also Legal Size], undated (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Greenberg, Samuel (Bernard) (1894-1917): MSS. D, undated (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Greenberg, Samuel (Bernard) (1894-1917): MSS. E - F, undated (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Greenberg, Samuel (Bernard) (1894-1917): MSS. G - K [see also Legal Size for Hindu Horizon and The Innate Stream], undated (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Greenberg, Samuel (Bernard) (1894-1917): MSS. L - N, undated (Box 74.5, Folder 1)
  - Greenberg, Samuel (Bernard) (1894-1917): MS. Love's Perfume, undated (Box 74.5, Folder 2)
  - Greenberg, Samuel (Bernard) (1894-1917): MS. Love's Perfume [photocopy], undated (Box 74.5, Folder 3)
  - Greenberg, Samuel (Bernard) (1894-1917): MS. Poems, undated (Box 74.5, Folder 4)
  - Greenberg, Samuel (Bernard) (1894-1917): MS. Poems [on a calendar], undated (Box 74.5, Folder 5)
  - Greenberg, Samuel (Bernard) (1894-1917): MSS. O - P [see also Legal Size for "Ode to a Trio"], undated (Box 74.5, Folder 6)
  - Greenberg, Samuel (Bernard) (1894-1917): MS. Poems [in album], undated (Box 74.5, Folder 7)
  - Greenberg, Samuel (Bernard) (1894-1917): MSS. Q - S [see also Legal Size for A Roomer Up Harlem; Sonnets from the Hebrew Temple; The Subject], undated (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Greenberg, Samuel (Bernard) (1894-1917): MSS. T - Z [see also Legal Size for Youth of the Orient], undated (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Greenberg, Samuel (Bernard) (1894-1917): MSS. Miscellaneous, undated (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Greenberg, Samuel (Bernard) (1894-1917): MSS. Miscellaneous [Titles for poems?], undated (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Greenberg, Samuel (Bernard) (1894-1917): MS. Notebook 1-3, undated (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Greenberg, Samuel (Bernard) (1894-1917): [Pictorial] Men 1, undated (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Greenberg, Samuel (Bernard) (1894-1917): MS. Notebook 4, undated (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Greenberg, Samuel (Bernard) (1894-1917): MS. Notebook 5-9, undated (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Greenberg, Samuel (Bernard) (1894-1917): MS. Notebook 10, undated (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Greenberg, Samuel (Bernard) (1894-1917): [Pictorial] Landscapes, undated (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Greenberg, Samuel (Bernard) (1894-1917): [Pictorial] Men 2, undated (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Greenberg, Samuel (Bernard) (1894-1917): [Pictorial oil] Self-Portrait?, undated (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Greenberg, Samuel (Bernard) (1894-1917): [Pictorial] Women, undated (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Greenberg, Samuel (Bernard) (1894-1917): [Pictorial 3 Self-Portraits] Sketchbook 1, undated (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Greenberg, Samuel (Bernard) (1894-1917): [Pictorial] Sketchbook 2, undated (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Greenberg, Samuel (Bernard) (1894-1917): [Pictorial] Photographs of S.B.G., undated (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Greenberg, Samuel (Bernard) (1894-1917): [Publications] Poems from the Greenberg MS. [edited by James Laughlin], undated (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Greeley, Horace (1811-1872), undated (Box 76, Folder 1a)
  - Green, Evelyn Everett, undated (Box 76, Folder 1b)
  - Green, Paul (1894- ), undated (Box 76, Folder 1c)
  - Green, Roger Lancelot (1918- ): MS. A Hundred Years of Children's Books, undated (Box 76, Folder 2a)
  - Green, Roger Lancelot (1918- ): MS. Trends in Children's Books, undated (Box 76, Folder 2b)
  - [Greenberg, Samuel (Bernard): see Boxes 74-75 & Legal Size 8], 1690-2000 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_f25f81bfebe08d00e66c6423b7fb7367)
  - Greenberger, Howard [and Robert Reinhold]: MS. 1, Our Play on the Future... [preliminary draft and notes], undated (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Greenberger, Howard [and Robert Reinhold]: MS. 2, Our Play on the Future... [1st draft, incomplete], undated (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Greenberger, Howard [and Robert Reinhold]: MS. 3, Our Play on the Future... [2nd draft], undated (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Greenberger, Howard [and Robert Reinhold]: MS. 4 Our Play on the Future... [photocopy w/ letter from Brooks Atkinson], undated (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Greene, Anne (Bosworth) (1877- ), undated (Box 76, Folder 7a)
  - Greene, Graham (1904- ), undated (Box 76, Folder 7b)
  - Greenland, George A.: [gift of Professor Joel Egerer, August 17, 1964], undated (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Greenough, Sara Dana (Loring) (1827-1885), undated (Box 76, Folder 9a)
  - Greenwood, Frederick (1830-1909), undated (Box 76, Folder 9b)
  - [Greenwood, Grace: see Lippincott, Sara Jane (Clarke), Box 110], 1690-2000 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_2b8a2de2d756ed475ea8f421808a73d4)
  - Greet, Clare, undated (Box 76, Folder 9c)
  - Gregory XVI, Pope (1765-1846): Signed Engraving, undated (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Gregory, Alyse, undated (Box 76, Folder 9e)
  - Greenwich Village: Ephemera, undated (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Gregory, Isabella Augusta (Persse), Lady: 7 Letters; 1 Mat., undated (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Greig, Maysie (1902- ), undated (Box 76, Folder 12a)
  - Grey, Edward Grey, 1st Viscount of Felloden (1862-1933), undated (Box 76, Folder 12b)
  - Grey, Zane (1872-1939), undated (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Grieve, Christopher M. (Hugh MacDiarmid): List of Holdings [see also Legal Size & Galleys], undated (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Grieve, Christopher M. (Hugh MacDiarmid): Correspondence [see also Legal Size], undated (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Grieve, Christopher M. (Hugh MacDiarmid): MS. Carotid Cornucopius [see also Legal Size & Galleys], undated (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Grieve, Christopher M. (Hugh MacDiarmid): MS. Carotid Cornucopius, undated (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Grieve, Christopher M. (Hugh MacDiarmid): MS. Carotid Cornucopius [early version of Section 1, also Section 1 & 2, Sections 1-4], undated (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Grieve, Christopher M. (Hugh MacDiarmid): MS. Carotid Cornucopius [Sections 1-4], undated (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Grieve, Christopher M. (Hugh MacDiarmid): MS. The Case of Alice Carruthers, undated (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Grieve, Christopher M. (Hugh MacDiarmid): MS. Hamilton Rotary Club Talk, undated (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Grieve, Christopher M. (Hugh MacDiarmid): MS. In the Gaelic Islands, undated (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Grieve, Christopher M. (Hugh MacDiarmid): MS. Lewis Grassic Gibbon, undated (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Grieve, Christopher M. (Hugh MacDiarmid): MS. M.M.C. Notes [2 notebooks], undated (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Grieve, Christopher M. (Hugh MacDiarmid): Printed Materials. The Present Condition of Scottish Arts and Affairs [Gift of Bart Auerbach, Jan. 1964], undated (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Grieve, Christopher M. (Hugh MacDiarmid): MS. Scottish Arts and Affairs [Scoto-Gaelic Literature], undated (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Grieve, Christopher M. (Hugh MacDiarmid): MS. Red Scotland, undated (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Grieve, Christopher M. (Hugh MacDiarmid): MS. Scotland and the United States of Europe, undated (Box 77, Folder 15a)
  - Grieve, Christopher M. (Hugh MacDiarmid): MS. Unique Typescript of Selected Poems of Hugh McDiarmid, undated (Box 77, Folder 15b)
  - Grieve, Christopher M. (Hugh MacDiarmid): MS. Introduction: Dunbar, William. Selected Poems, undated (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Grieve, Christopher M. (Hugh MacDiarmid): [Grieve, Christopher M.] Trevlyn, Valda: Hugh MacDiarmid and the Scottish Landscape, undated (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Grieve, Christopher M. (Hugh MacDiarmid): [Pictorial] Original Drawing by Stephen Spurrier, undated (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Grigson, Baseley H.: 14 A.L.s., undated (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Griswold, Rufus W., undated (Box 78, Folder 2a)
  - Grote, George (1794-1871), undated (Box 78, Folder 2b)
  - Grote, Harriet (1792-1878), undated (Box 78, Folder 2c)
  - Grove, Sir George (1820-1900), undated (Box 78, Folder 3a)
  - Guerland, Albert Leon (1880-), undated (Box 78, Folder 3b)
  - Guillot, Adolphe, undated (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Guiney, Louise Imogen (1861-1920), undated (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Guiterman, Arthur: MS. Poems [published, in alphabetical order], undated (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Guiterman, Arthur: MS. Poems [see also Legal Size for pre-1909], undated (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Guiterman, Arthur: MS. Poems [published, not in books, A-H], undated (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Guiterman, Arthur: MS. Poems [published, not in books, I-Z], undated (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Guiterman, Arthur: MS. Poems [unpublished?, A-O], undated (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Guiterman, Arthur: MS. Poems [unpublished, P-Z], undated (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Gull, Cyril Arthur E.R. (1876-1923), undated (Box 78, Folder 12a)
  - Gunn, Neil Miller (1891- ), undated (Box 78, Folder 12b)
  - Gunter, Archibald Clavering (1847-1907), undated (Box 78, Folder 12c)
  - Guthrie, Charles John Guthrie, Lord (1849-1920): MS. R.L.S. at College, undated (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Guthrie, Thomas Anstey (1856-1934), undated (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Gwynn, Stephen Lucius (1864-1950), undated (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Habberton, John (1842-1921), undated (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Habberton, John (1842-1921): MS. The Hypocrisy of Pull, undated (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Haggard, Henry Rider, Sir (1856-1925): 1882-1923 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Haggard, Henry Rider, Sir (1856-1925): Miscellaneous Correspondence [see also Legal Size], undated (Box 79, Folder 4a)
  - Haggard, Lilias Rider: 1 A.L.s., MS. [Mat], undated (Box 79, Folder 4b)
  - Haggard, Henry Rider, Sir (1856-1925): MS. Beatrice [Galley to Adv., 1894], undated (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Haight, Gordon S., undated (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Hale, Edward Everett (1822-1909): 1845-1875 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Hale, Edward Everett (1822-1909): 1880-1892; undated (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Hale, Sarah Josepha (Buell) (1788-1879), undated (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Halegua, Lillian: MS. The Priest plus 2 A.L.s., 1966 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Halegua, Lillian: MS. [carbon] The Priest, undated (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Halford, John, undated (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Haliburton, Thomas Chandler (1796-1865), undated (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Hall, Anna Maria (1800-1881), undated (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Hall, Basil (1788-1844), undated (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Hall, James Norman (1887-1951): 2 A.L.s., undated (Box 79, Folder 16a)
  - Hall, Radclyffe (188?-1943): 1 A.L.s., undated (Box 79, Folder 16b)
  - Hall, Samuel Carter (1800-1889): 4 A.L.s., undated (Box 79, Folder 16c)
  - Hallam, Henry (1777-1859), undated (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Halleck, Fitz-Greene (1790-1867), undated (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Halliwell-Phillipps, James Orchard (1820-1889), undated (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - Hamerton, Philip Gilbert (1834-1894), undated (Box 79, Folder 20a)
  - Hamilton, Cosmo, undated (Box 79, Folder 20b)
  - [Hamilton, Gail: see Dodge, Mary Abigail, Box 46], 1690-2000 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_979afb467d3694e9112927aebc62ae51)
  - Hamilton, Marie, undated (Box 79, Folder 20c)
  - Hamilton, William Rowen, Sir (1805-1865), undated (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Hammond, Christine M. Demain (fl. 1886-1910): Pictorial, The Absentee [1894, 10 pp. proofs] (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Hammond, Christine M. Demain (fl. 1886-1910): Pictorial, The Absentee [1894, 11 pp. proofs] (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Hammond, Christine M. Demain (fl. 1886-1910): Pictorial, The Absentee [1894, 11 pp. proofs] (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Hammond, Christine M. Demain (fl. 1886-1910): Pictorial, Castle Rackrent [1894, 19 pp. proof] (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Hammond, Christine M. Demain (fl. 1886-1910): Pictorial, Marmonte's Moral Tales [1895, 36 drawings] (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Hammond, Christine M. Demain (fl. 1886-1910): Pictorial, The Good Natured Man [1896, 15 pp. proofs] (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Hammond, Christine M. Demain (fl. 1886-1910): Pictorial, She Stoops to Conquer, undated (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Hammond, Christine M. Demain (fl. 1886-1910): Pictorial, She Stoops to Conquer, undated (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Hammond, Christine M. Demain (fl. 1886-1910): Pictorial [removed from] She Stoops to Conquer, undated (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Hammond, Christine M. Demain (fl. 1886-1910), undated (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Hammond, Christine M. Demain (fl. 1886-1910), undated (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Hammond, Christine M. Demain (fl. 1886-1910), undated (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Hammond, Christine M. Demain (fl. 1886-1910), undated (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Hammond, Christine M. Demain (fl. 1886-1910), undated (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Hamper, William (1776-1831), undated (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Hankin, St. John Emile Clavering (1869-1909): 2 Letters, undated (Box 81, Folder 2a)
  - Hanley, James (1901- ): 5 Letters [see also Oversize, 2 Letters], undated (Box 81, Folder 2b)
  - Hanley, Jennifer: 1 Letter, undated (Box 81, Folder 2c)
  - Hanline, Maurice A.: Fragments of Fears and Other Poems and Plays, undated (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Hapgood, Isabel Florence (1850-1928), undated (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Harben, William Nathaniel (1858-1919): 1 Letter, 1 Photograph., undated (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - [Hardy, Thomas: see Boxes 82 & 82.5], 1690-2000 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_bd38ededa2714999031be2aab268bc9c)
  - Hare, Augustus J. C. (1834-1903): 5 Letters, undated (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Harland, Henry (1861-1905): 1 Letter to Miss Curtis [May 9th], 1 Letter to Edmund Gosse [June 21, 1903], 1 Letter to Mrs. Leverson [October 23, 1895], 1895-1903 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - [Harland, Marion: see Terhune, Mary Virginia Hawes, Boxes 177 & Legal Size 17], 1690-2000 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_396f7adaa19e43b83417a4e606fbbf7c)
  - Harlow, Alvin F.: 1 Mat. The Devil's Hopper [unpublished], undated (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Harraden, Beatrice (1864-1936): undated [2 of 2] (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Harraden, Beatrice (1864-1936): 1894-1919 [1 of 2] (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Harris, Corra, undated (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - [Harris, Frank: see Boxes 83-86.2], 1690-2000 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_52dc794aee497bb9c787991f00fe0ea2)
  - Hardy, Florence Emily (1881-1937); Hardy, Emma Lavinia Gifford (1840-1912): undated; 1894; 1924 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Hardy, Henry: Life of Thomas Hardy, 1916 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Hardy, Thomas (1840-1928): Addenda, undated (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Hardy, Thomas (1840-1928): MATs., undated (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Hardy, Thomas (1840-1928): Correspondence [1877-1899] (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Hardy, Thomas (1840-1928): Correspondence [1900-1909] (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Hardy, Thomas (1840-1928): Correspondence [1910-1921] (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Hardy, Thomas (1840-1928): MS. Among the Roman Gravemounds [see also Oversize], undated (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Hardy, Thomas (1840-1928): Tess of the T'Ubervilles [Drama; Box Office, 1897] (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Hardy, Thomas (1840-1928): Tess of the T'Ubervilles [Drama; Box Office, January -April 1898] (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Hardy, Thomas (1840-1928): Tess of the T'Ubervilles [Drama; Box Office, October -December 1898] (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Hardy, Thomas (1840-1928): Tess of the T'Ubervilles [Drama; Treasurer's Statement, 1898] (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Hardy, Thomas (1840-1928): Tess of the T'Ubervilles [Drama; Box Office, January 1899- ] (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Hardy, Thomas (1840-1928): ca. 1920s; undated (Box 82.5, Folder 1)
  - Hardy, Thomas (1840-1928): Pictorial, undated (Box 82.5, Folder 2)
  - Hardy, Thomas (1840-1928): Greeting Cards, undated (Box 82.5, Folder 3)
  - Hardy, Thomas (1840-1928): Jezreel the Master [note to Clement Short enclosed]; Two Phantasies, undated (Box 82.5, Folder 4)
  - [Hardy, Thomas]: Memorial Service to T.H.; Letters re Memorial Service, undated (Box 82.5, Folder 5)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Correspondence, undated (Box 83, Folder 1a)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Correspondence to A - Z, undated (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Correspondence to Pearson, Hesketh [see also Legal Size], undated (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Correspondence to Ross, Arthur L., undated (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Correspondence to Shaw, G. B. [see also Legal Size], undated (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Correspondence to White, Maurice, 1919-1929 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Correspondence from A - Z, undated (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Correspondence from Alice, Princess of Monaco [copies], undated (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Correspondence from Churchill, Winston [copies], undated (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Printed Matter, undated (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Butterworth / Landau, Hammel, undated (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Nellie Harris / A. E. Ross, 1927-1954 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Nellie Harris, Miscellaneous, undated (Box 83.5, Folder 1)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Lyngklip, Pauline and Einar, undated (Box 83.5, Folder 2)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Ross, A. L., Letters to A.L.R., undated (Box 83.5, Folder 3)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Ross, A. L. / Mrs. Patrick Campbell, undated (Box 83.5, Folder 4)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Ross, A. L., Letters to A.L.R.; Henry Miller, undated (Box 83.5, Folder 5)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Ross, A. L. / Hesketh Pearson Correspondence, undated (Box 83.5, Folder 6)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Ross, A. L. [Business], undated (Box 83.5, Folder 7)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Ross, A. L. [Business]; Montes the Matador [film], undated (Box 83.5, Folder 8)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Ross, A. L. [Business]; My Life and Loves [see also Legal Size], undated (Box 83.5, Folder 9)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Ross, A. L. [Business]; Oscar Wilde Lawsuit [Stokes v. Harris], undated (Box 83.5, Folder 10)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Ross, A. L. [Business]; Reminiscences of a Cowboy [motion picture], undated (Box 83.5, Folder 11)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Ross, A. L. [Business]; Shaw, Collected Letters, undated (Box 83.5, Folder 12)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Tarbeaux, Frank; Tarboy, undated (Box 83.5, Folder 13)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Petition to the French Court, undated (Box 83.5, Folder 14)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Clippings, undated (Box 83.5, Folder 15)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Photographs, Negatives, undated (Box 83.5, Folder 16)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Miscellaneous Printed Material, undated (Box 83.5, Folder 17)